{
    "data": [
        {
            "cards": [
                {
                    "id": 1,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "One",
                        "front": "一"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 2,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Two",
                        "front": "二"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 3,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Three",
                        "front": "三"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 4,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Four",
                        "front": "四"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 5,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Five",
                        "front": "五"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 6,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Six",
                        "front": "六"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 7,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Seven",
                        "front": "七"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 8,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Eight",
                        "front": "八"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 9,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Nine",
                        "front": "九"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 10,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Ten",
                        "front": "十"
                    }
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "cards": [
                {
                    "id": 1,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Red",
                        "front": "赤"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 2,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Blue",
                        "front": "青"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 3,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Green",
                        "front": "緑"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 4,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Orange",
                        "front": "オレンジ"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 5,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Purple",
                        "front": "紫"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 6,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Yellow",
                        "front": "黄色"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 7,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Black",
                        "front": "黒"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 8,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "White",
                        "front": "白"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 9,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Brown",
                        "front": "茶色"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 10,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Pink",
                        "front": "ピンク"
                    }
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "cards": [
                {
                    "id": 1,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "to eat",
                        "front": "食べる"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 2,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "to drink",
                        "front": "飲む"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 3,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "to sleep",
                        "front": "寝る"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 4,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "to get up",
                        "front": "起きる"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 5,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "to read",
                        "front": "読む"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 6,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "to wear",
                        "front": "着る"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 7,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "to laugh",
                        "front": "笑う"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 8,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "to dance",
                        "front": "踊る"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 9,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "to run",
                        "front": "走る"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 10,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "to walk",
                        "front": "歩く"
                    }
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "cards": [
                {
                    "id": 1,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Big",
                        "front": "大きい"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 2,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Small",
                        "front": "小さい"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 3,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Slow",
                        "front": "遅い"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 4,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Fast",
                        "front": "速い"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 5,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Near",
                        "front": "近く"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 6,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Far",
                        "front": "遠い"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 7,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Good",
                        "front": "良い"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 8,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Bad",
                        "front": "悪い"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 9,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Many",
                        "front": "多い"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 10,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Few",
                        "front": "少し"
                    }
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}